invitationconsultants.com 2010-03-05

# Help Center at InvitationConsultants.com - Security & Privacy

* * *

**Credit Card Security**   
The Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard ("PCI Standard") is intended to protect cardholders' credit card account and transaction information. Invitation Consultants, Inc. has been   
certified "PCI Compliant" by MacAfee®. 

Click here to verify: 

* * *

## Privacy Notice: 

_Last updated: 2/9/2010_ | [ ](http://www.truste.com/ivalidate.php?url=www.invitationconsultants.com&sealid=101) | 

Invitation Consultants, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers www.invitationconsultants.com and www.graduation-announcements-store.com (collectively "the site").   
  
---|---  
  
Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Service at [customerservice@invitationconsultants.com](mailto:customerservice@invitationconsultants.com).  
  
If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe - [http://www.truste.com/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](https://www.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint) TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. Thanks for shopping at www.invitationconsultants.com. We've done our best to ensure the security and privacy of your transactions with us. Be confident that your credit card information and other personal data will be regarded with the highest standards of confidentiality, safety, and security.  

(back to top)

* * *

## Information, Collection & Use

**Registration** \- We do not require registration to use our site. 

**Orders**

****If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

Credit card numbers and expiration dates are processed immediately and are not stored on our computer systems. 

**Referral program**

****If you choose to use our referral service to e-mail a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Invitation Consultants, Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [customerservice@invitationconsultants.com](mailto:customerservice@invitationconsultants.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

In the "My Account" Address Book functionality when you enter names and addresses for a third party, we will collect that third party's name and mailing address information, so that we can facilitate the mailing per your request. We will not use this information for any other purpose. 

(back to top)

* * *

## Uses of Information

**Communications from the Site** _Special Offers and Updates_

****We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You will only receive such information if you previously bought products from Invitation Consultants, Inc.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out." 

_Customer Service_

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to confirm your order. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries and to provide the services you request. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. You will also get an email to let you know when your proof is ready, when your order ships out. You might also get an e-mail requesting your feedback, after you have received your order.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure** _Agents/Service Providers_

****We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, and a third party service provider to provide live chat service. We use iContact to provide you with e-mails about special offers and promotions. When you place an order with us, we will share your e-mail address as necessary for them to provide that service. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

 _BLOG/Testimonial_

****If you post a comment to our blog or post a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

 _Legal Disclaimer_

****We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for any promotional purpose. 

(back to top)

* * *

## Choice / Opt Out / Access

****If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at customerservice@invitationconsultants.com.

You can also opt-out of promotional communications and update or correct your information by logging into "My Account" on the site and clicking on "Account Settings".

(back to top)

* * *

## Log Files

****A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information, except to prevent fraud or abuse of our systems. 

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate usage volume statistics to track website performance. 

(back to top)

* * *

## Cookies

****As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, and date/time stamp.  
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.   
We use persistent cookies set by one of our service providers only to measure and track the effectiveness of certain marketing campaigns.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as your shopping cart, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only. 

(back to top)

* * *

## Links to Other Sites

****This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Invitation Consultants, Inc. Please be aware that we, Invitation Consultants, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

(back to top)

* * *

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Authentic Sites, like www.invitationconsultants.com, use Thawte SSL Web Server Certificates to offer secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the site. Thawte has checked and verified the company's registration documents and the site's registered domain name. When entering a quote, you will see a little padlock on the bottom of your browser. By double-clicking on the padlock, you will see the Certificate issued by Thawte to Invitation Consultants, Inc. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email to us at [customerservice@invitationconsultants.com.](emailto:customerservice@invitationconsultants.com)   
  
(back to top)

* * *

## Business Transitions

In the event Invitation Consultants, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.(back to top)

* * *

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Invitation Consultants, Inc.  ** |  8180 Woodland Center Blvd.  |  Tampa, FL 33614 

(back to top)
